libertysafe.com 2018-12-29

# Liberty Safes - Security and Privacy

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy. 

#### What Personal Information We Collect

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using the Libertysafe.com Web site. This information can include your name, street address, and phone number when you order a Safe on the site. We may also ask for personal information when you contact our Customer Service. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity. 

#### Purchase Information

When you make order a safe we collect your name, your billing address and phone number. We collect this information in order submit your order to an authorized Liberty dealer close to you.

#### Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you order a safe at Liberty Safe.com you will be assigned a cookie (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you with your shopping basket. 

#### How We Use Your Personal Information

Information we collect on Libertysafe.com may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways: 

  * Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests
  * Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices 
  * Find and stock the products you want 
  * Customize your shopping experience
  * Define your safe order for an authorized Liberty dealer

#### When and With Whom We Share Your Personal Information

We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We will share personal customer information only with our agents, representatives and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes, including fulfilling customer orders; offering certain products and services in connection with our Web site; communicating to customers; providing customer service; enhancing and improving customers' shopping experience; enabling access to our partners' sites; providing a personalized shopping experience; and completing credit card transactions. 

Aside from the purposes described above, we will never share your personal information with any other third parties unless we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the disclosure is required by law. We may share aggregated demographic and statistical information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

#### More About Your Privacy

We realize that making purchases at Libertysafe.com, or any other Web site, requires trust on your part. We value your trust very highly, and pledge to you, our customer, that we will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and that your personal information will only be used as set forth in this Policy. This includes your name, address, phone number, and/or email address, credit-, in addition to any other personal information that can be linked to you, personally.

We believe that you have a right to know, before shopping at Libertysafe.com, or at any other time, exactly what information we might collect from you, why we collect it and how we use it.

#### Changes to Liberty Safe’s Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. If we make any significant change to this policy, we will post notice of the change on Libertysafe.com. for a period of at least six months after the change is implemented. 

#### Contacting Libertysafe.com

We will use your email address to respond to your questions, suggestions, and/or requests for assistance in using our site. For questions or comments regarding this policy, you may contact Liberty Safe and Security Products, Inc. at: 

Email: webmaster@libertysafe.com  
Phone: 1-800-247-5625  
Mail: Liberty Safe and Security Products, Inc.   
1199 West Utah Avenue  
Payson, UT 84651
